let questionsVerbal = [
    {
      numb: 1,
      question: " We _____ a lovely three weeks in the south of Spain last year.",
      answer: "spent",
      options: [
        "took",
        "did",
        "spent",
        "passed",
      ],
    },
    {
        numb: 2,
        question:  "Please don't forget to message me when you _____ home.",
        answer: "get",
        options: [
            "will get",
            "get",
            "are going to get",
            "are getting",
        ],
      },
      {
        numb: 3,
        question: "The teacher asked if _____ to bring our textbooks to class.",
        answer: "we had all remembered",        
        
        options: [
          "all we had remembered",
          "we had all remembered",                   
          "had all we remembered",
          "had we all remembered",
        ],
      },
      {
        numb: 4,
        question: "I must ____ for being so late.",
        answer: "pardon",      
        options: [
          "regret",
          "apologise",
          "excuse",
          "pardon",
        ],
      },
      {
        numb: 5,
        question: "I've only got a ____ money in the bank",
        answer: "few",
        options: [
       
         "less",
         "little",
         "few",
         "bit",
        ],
      },
      {
        numb: 6,
        question: " We _____ a lovely three weeks in the south of Spain last year.",
        answer: "are",
        options: [
            
          "are",
            "do",
            "have",
            "will",
          
        ],
      },
      {
        numb: 7,
        question: "Would you like to _____ for shopping with me this afternoon?",
        answer: "go",
        options: [
          
          "go",
          "do",
          "make",
          "get",
         
        ],
      },
      {
        numb: 8,
        question: "I'm very ____ could I have a glass of water ,please?",
        answer: "thirsty",
        options: [
        
         "empty",
         "thirsty",//ans
         "hungry",
         "dirty",
 
          
         
        ],
      },

      {
        numb: 9,
        question: "Would you like to _____ for shopping with me this afternoon?",
        answer: "go",
        options: [
          
          "go",
          "do",
          "make",
          "get",
         
        ],
      },

      {
        numb: 10,
        question: "Would you like to _____ for shopping with me this afternoon?",
        answer: "go",
        options: [
          
          "go",
          "do",
          "make",
          "get",
         
        ],
      },


]